There's a feeling you get on the ice.
은반 위에서만 느낄 수 있는 기분이 있어요.
It's magic.
마법 같죠.
I haven't felt that magic in a long time.
그 마법 같은 기분을 느낀 지 정말 오래됐어요.
After Freddie, it was never the same.
프레디 이후로는 모든 게 예전 같지 않았죠.
Hi.
안녕.
Wonder how you're doing,
네가 어떻게 지내는지 궁금했어,
with Freddie coming back here to train with Riley.
프레디가 라일리와 훈련하러 이곳으로 돌아온다는데 말이야.
Partnerships are business decisions, not romances.
파트너십은 비즈니스적인 결정이지, 로맨스가 아니에요.
You can skate with whoever you want.
누구와 스케이트를 타든 그건 네 자유야.
Apparently, Brayden Elliot's looking for someone to skate with.
듣자하니 브레이든 엘리엇이 함께할 파트너를 찾고 있다더군.
-Hey. -He's a cocky idiot.
-안녕. -그 사람은 거만한 바보예요.
He's practically a ticket to the Olympics
그와 파트너가 되는 사람은 누구든 올림픽 행 티켓을
for whoever he pairs with.
거의 따놓은 거나 다름없어.
You understand I'm gonna bring the right partner
내가 제대로 된 파트너를 시상대 꼭대기까지
to the top of the podium?
데려다줄 거라는 거 이해하지?
Just try it.
그냥 한번 해봐.
See how it feels.
어떤 기분인지 느껴봐.
Freddie's the love of your life.
프레디는 네 인생의 사랑이잖아.
You dropped me as your skating partner.
넌 내 스케이팅 파트너 자리를 내팽개쳤어.
All I can do is say that I am sorry.
내가 할 수 있는 말은 미안하다는 것뿐이야.
We gotta get used to one another,
우린 서로에게 익숙해져야 해,
and we can't do that unless we trust each other.
그리고 서로를 신뢰하지 않으면 그럴 수 없지.
I wanna win Worlds,
난 세계 선수권에서 우승하고 싶어,
and I wanna win it with you.
그리고 너와 함께 우승하고 싶어.
You're lucky to have her.
그녀를 얻은 건 네 행운이야.
Is this the part where you tell me if I hurt her,
내가 그녀에게 상처를 주면 가만두지 않겠다고
you're gonna come after me?
협박이라도 하려는 거야?
We're competitors now. Given our history, it's probably best
우린 이제 경쟁자야. 우리 과거를 생각하면, 그냥
if we just keep things professional, you know?
비즈니스적으로만 대하는 게 최선일 것 같아.
Is that really what you want?
그게 정말 네가 원하는 거야?
It's what's best.
이게 최선이야.
Let's go win Worlds.
가서 세계 선수권 우승하자.
Why did you say that thing about feeling the magic?
마법 같은 기분이라는 말은 왜 한 거야?
It's not about feeling anything.
기분을 느끼는 게 중요한 게 아니야.
If you wanna win,
이기고 싶다면,
then this is what you have to do.
이게 네가 해야 할 일이야.